Lesson 22. By heart, some plays are so successful that they run for years on end.
第22课。从心中，有些戏剧是如此成功，以至于他们连续多年奔跑。
In many ways, this is unfortunate for the poor actors who are required to go on repeating the same
在许多方面，对于要求继续重复同样的贫穷演员来说，这是不幸的
part: n.   剧中的角色，台词
line's night. After night, one would expect them to know their parts by heart and never have
线的夜晚。夜晚后，人们会期望他们内心了解自己的各个部分，并且永远不会
falter: v.   支吾，结巴说
caused a falter. Yet this is not always the case. A famous actor in a highly successful play was
导致步履蹒跚。但是并非总是如此。一位非常成功的戏剧中的著名演员是
role: n.   角色, aristocrat: n.   贵族, imprison: v.   关押, Bastille: n.   巴士底狱
once cast in the role of an aristocrat who had been imprisoned in the Bastille for 20 years.
曾经扮演过一个贵族的角色，该贵族在巴士底狱中被囚禁了20年。
In the last act, a jailer would always come on to the stage with a letter which he would hand to
在最后一幕中，一位狱卒总是带着一封信给他交给的信
the prisoner. Even though the noble was expected to read the letter at each performance,
囚犯。即使预计贵族会在每次演出中阅读这封信，但
he always insisted that it should be written out in full. One night, the jailer decided to play a
他总是坚持认为应该全部写出。一天晚上，狱卒决定扮演
colleague: n.   同事
joke on his colleague to find out if. After so many performances, he had managed to learn the
在他的同事开玩笑，以找出是否。经过如此多的表演，他设法学习了
curtain: n.   （舞台上的）幕布, reveal: v.   使显露
contents of the letter by heart. The curtain went up on the final act of the play and revealed
字母的内容。幕布在剧本的最后一幕中升起，并揭示了
aristocrat: n.   贵族, cell: n.   单人监房，监号
the aristocrat sitting alone behind. Bars in his dark cell. Just then, the jailer appeared with
贵族独自坐在身后。在他黑暗的牢房里的酒吧。就在这时，狱卒与
aristocrat: n.   贵族, cell: n.   单人监房，监号
the precious letter in his bands. He entered the cell and presented the letter to the aristocrat,
乐队中的宝贵信。他进入牢房，并向贵族赠送这封信，
blank: adj. 空白的
but the copy he gave him had not been written out in full as usual. It was simply a blank sheet of
但是他给他的副本并没有像往常一样全部写出来。只是一张空白的床单
lines: n.   （剧本中的）台词
paper. The jailer looked on eagerly. Anxious to see if his fellow actor had at last learned his lines.
纸。狱卒热切地看着。渴望看看他的同伴终于学会了他的台词。
blank: adj. 空白的, squint: v.   眯着（眼）看，瞄
The noble stared at the blank sheet of paper for a few seconds. Then, squinting his eyes,
贵族盯着空白纸几秒钟。然后，斜视他的眼睛，
dim: adj. 昏暗
he said, the light is dim, read the letter to me. And he promptly handed the sheet of paper to
他说，光线很暗，读给我的信。他迅速将纸交给了
the jailer, finding that he could not remember a word of the letter either. The jailer replied,
狱卒发现他也不记得这封信的话。狱卒回答，
dim: adj. 昏暗
the light is indeed dim. Sire, I must get my glasses. With this, he hurried off the stage.
光确实很昏暗。父亲，我必须戴上眼镜。因此，他急忙离开舞台。
aristocrat: n.   贵族
Much to the aristocrat's amusement. The jailer returned a few moments later with a pair of glasses
贵族的娱乐很大。囚犯片刻后用一副眼镜返回
proceed: v.   继续进行
and the usual copy of the letter. With he proceeded to read to the prisoner.
以及这封信的通常副本。随着他开始向囚犯读书。